So, the exercise asked us to put this
所以这次演习让我们把这个
angle's variable with a long list of numbers in it right here.
角度的变量在这里有一个长的数字
Then we needed to write a loop that would use the values from that list.
然后 我们需要编写一个循环 该循环将使用该列表中的值
The loop started for angle in angles,
这个线圈开始角度的角度
and then we had to write the statements inside the loop.
然后我们要在环线内写下这些语句
Inside the loop, we wanted the turtle to turn right, but how far?
在这个圈里 我们想让海龟右转 但是多远呢 ?
On each step, we wanted to turn by an angle that's been taken from this list.
在每一步上 我们都想用一个从这个列表中获取的角度来转变
There's a variable created by the loop that will do just that.
由循环创建的变量将仅执行该变量
This is the angle variable.
这是角度变量
So, to get the turtle named builder to turn right by that angle,
所以要让乌龟叫建设者按那个角度右转
we say builder.right (angle).
我们说的是 builder.right (角度 )
Remember, each time the loop runs,
记住每次循环运行
this variable will get assigned an item from this list.
此变量将从该列表中分配一个项
The first time through the loop the variable get assigned negative 90,
第一次通过循环将变量分配为负 90
the second time through the loop it'll get zero.
第二次它就会归零
So, it won't turn at all,
所以它根本不会转动
then zero again, then negative 90 and so on.
然后再零 再负 90 等
After it turns we want it to go forward 25.
我们想让它前进 25
We know how to do that builder.forward(25).
我们知道如何执行 builder.forward (25)
Let's run this code and see what happens.
让我们运行这个代码 看看发生了什么
Hey, look.
嘿看啊
It looks like a house, or maybe an arrow.
它看起来像房子 或者可能是箭
So, this program shows us something interesting about numbers.
所以 这个节目给我们展示了一些关于数字的有趣的东西
They can mean different things depending on how they're used.
根据它们的使用方式 它们可以表示不同的东西
In the code that you've seen in this course,
在你在这个过程中看到的代码中
we've used a list of numbers to mean several different things.
我们用了一串数字来表示几种不同的东西
In the very first examples with George and Amy,
在乔治和艾米的第一个例子中
the actual numbers in the list weren't used at all.
列表中的实际数字根本没有使用
We just use the list length to control how many sides the turtle drew;
我们只是用列表长度来控制海龟画的多少边 ;
four sides for a square,
一个正方形的四边
or five for a pentagon.
五个五个五个
On the page with Dizzy,
在有 Dizzy的页面上
the turtle who drew a blue square spiral,
画出蓝色方形螺旋的乌龟
we used the numbers in the list to control the lengths of the side.
我们用了列表中的数字来控制边的长度
Here, building this house,
在这里建造这座房子
we're using the numbers to control the angles of the turtle's turns.
我们用数字来控制海龟的角度
The number 90 could be used as a length or as an angle.
编号 90 可用作长度或角度
If we pass 90 to the forward method,
如果我们将 90 传递到正向方法
then the turtle treats it as a length.
那乌龟会把它当成一个长度
But if we pass it to the right or left method the turtle treats it as an angle.
但如果我们把它传给右边或左边的方法 乌龟会把它当作一个角度
This is something you will see over and over in your future as a programmer.
这是你未来作为一个程序员会看到的东西
A values type doesn't tell you everything about the meaning of that value.
值类型不告诉您该值的含义
It's up to you as the programmer to think through whether
由你作为程序员来思考
a particular numerical value is meant to be a distance,
一个数值就是一个距离
an angle, account, an amount of money, or something else.
一个角度 账户 一笔钱 或者别的什么